本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
圣  城  风  云
『第一季  第二集』
翻译  Jasmine雪
翻译  LyraL
翻译  ala365
翻译  小熊嘟嘟
翻译  小舞
时间轴  veryink
校对  苏小黛
后期  渔夫
特效  WiLL
中转  渔夫
总监制  苏小黛
上帝  请赐予你衷心的仆人安息
O Lord, grant eternal rest and let everlasting
让永恒之光照耀她
light shine upon your servant here
将她从永恒的死亡中解救出来
and deliver her from eternal death in that awful day,
她当天的遭遇堪令天地震颤
when the heavens and the earth shall be shaken
请以地狱之火来审判这个世界  阿门
and thou shalt come to judge the world by fire. Amen.
阿门
Amen.
等等
Wait.
这是我的错
It's my fault.
-不是的  -事实如此
- No.   - But it is.
别让这种情绪掌控你
Don't let it rule you.
洛特杀她就是为了让你屈服
Lot murdered her so you would buckle.
要化悲痛为力量
Take what you're feeling and use it as fuel.
我们会成功的
We'll make this right.
但你不能分心  现在正直危急关头
But you can't be distracted; there's too much at stake.
我们得立即返回卡米洛特
We need to return to Camelot now.
不行
No.
不要
No!
我想...独自和她待一会儿
I want to stay with her... on my own.
给你个命令  好好部署我们的防御
I'm giving you an order. Plan my defences.
我会在日落前回来
I'll return before sundown.
现在让我安静的待会儿
Now leave me to make my peace.
你用这把剑杀过多少人
How many have you killed with this?
你觉得我会数吗
You think I keep count?
你又在想亚瑟那小子了  是吧
You're thinking about the boy again, aren't you?
我以为他听懂我的警告了
I thought he understood my warning.
你给过他机会了
You gave him a chance.
我们做得很公正  别再想了
You were fair. Don't brood.
她是他母亲
She was his mother.
他还有个备用的  不是吗
He has a spare, doesn't he?
还记得你父母是什么时候过世的吗
Do you remember when your parents died?
当然  是我杀了他们
Yes. I killed them.
现在我们是要哀悼通往胜利路上的尸体
Now are we going to mourn the corpse that gave us the victory,
还是要庆祝我们联盟的雄厚力量呢
or celebrate the strength of our unity.
很快  那小子就会消失
Soon, the boy will be gone,
你我就将登上王位
and you and I will have the throne.
我们得迅速行动起来
We need to move fast.
离洛特王进攻还有四天时间
We now have four dawns before King Lot will attack.
要加强防御体系的方方面面
Strengthen every aspect of our defences.
在所有出入口加派守卫
More guards at all exits and entrances.
盘问所有不认识的人
Challenge anyone you don't recognize.
不要相信任何人
Trust no one.
我们没有足够的兵力
We don't have enough forces.
我会解决
Leave that to me.
你们当前的首要任务就是保护亚瑟
As of now, you have one single priority, protect Arthur.
保护你们未来的国王
Protect your future king.
你这是干嘛
What're you doing?
你刚才盯着我看
You were staring at me.
我来这里就是不想被人盯着看
And this is where I go not to be stared at!
我可以解释
I can explain.
继续说
Go on then.
我做了个梦
I had a dream.
可能是幻想...是你从海里走出来的景象
Maybe a vision... of you... walking out of the sea.
少来
No!
我很清楚这里现在的情况
I know what goes on around these lands now.
你休想动我一分
And you are not going to lay a finger on me.
不管这里有什么情况
Whatever's going on round here,
我都没有参与  我发誓
I'm not a part of it, I swear.
我是逃避到这里来的
I came to get away.
然后你...出现了
And then you ... appeared.
逃避什么
Get away from what?
我刚安葬了我母亲  在上面的山上
I buried my mother. On the hill above.
她昨天被杀害了
She was murdered yesterday.
不信的话  你可以去看看坟墓
You can go see the grave if you don't believe me.
她怎么过世的
How did she die?
一个叫洛特的军阀杀了她
A warrior called Lot killed her.
为什么杀她
Why did he kill her?
因为我杀了他儿子
I killed his son.
我明白了  接下来他会杀了你
I see. He'll come for you next.
我的家人  叔叔们  曾经对抗过他
My family, my uncles, they stood up to him once.
他把他们都杀了  他不会收手的
He killed them all. He won't stop.
所以我必须比他强大
So I must be stronger than him.
不可能
You can't be.
我必须做到
I have to be.
那个梦  梦到我的那个梦
This dream, the one I was in.
结果怎样
How did it end?
我不记得了
I can't remember.
亚瑟
Arthur!
是我父亲  我以为他们把他也杀了
It's my father. I thought they'd killed him too.
我得走了  很抱歉
I have to go. I'm sorry.
我叫亚瑟
I'm Arthur.
祝你好运  亚瑟
Good luck, Arthur.
可我还不知道你的名字
But I don't know your name.
是的  你不知道
No. You don't.
父亲
Father!
我以为你也死了
I thought you were dead.
他们俘虏了我们俩
They came and they took us both.
我逃了出来  我让你母亲失望了
I managed to escape. I let your mother down.
不
No.
是我低估了洛特的能力
I misjudged what Lot was capable of.
责任在我
I bear the responsibility.
那你就帮我们吧  帮我们为她的死复仇
Then you help us. Help us avenge her death.
我们不能以死相争  而要以智取胜
Now we'll fight... not by blood, by guile.
听我的指挥  她不会白白牺牲的
Follow me and she won't have died in vain.
你在哪
Where are you?
尤瑟已死  但是又冒出来一个
Uther is dead. But there's another.
尤瑟的儿子
Uther's boy.
这不会改变什么
It makes no difference.
他现在一无所有  他母亲也被杀了
He has nothing now. His mother was killed.
他的锐气已挫
His spirit is broken.
时机就要到了
It's nearly the time.
我发誓
I swear.
你今天有个重要的任务
You've a big task today.
你每天都这么说
You say that every day.
今天这个是最重要的
This is your biggest.
你知道他在说什么吗
D'you know what he's talking about?
不知道  但他说你需要我
Nope. He said you'd need me.
不过话说回来  你一直都是需要我的
But then, you always need me!
才没有呢
I don't think so.
国王的存在主要是一个概念
A king exists primarily as an idea.
我们要说服人们去相信你做为国王的概念
We persuade the people to believe in the idea of you,
然后再把它变成现实
then we can make it a reality.
里昂提斯也会一起来
Leontes will join us.
他有你用得到的装备
He has the equipment you'll need.
什么装备  你在说什么啊
What equipment? What're you talking about?
是啊  我要怎么成为一个新的概念呢
Yeah, how do I become a new idea?
你要做到不可能的事
By doing the impossible.
罗马人认为那剑
The Romans believed that sword
属于马尔斯  他们的战神
belonged to Mars, their God of War.
我们知道这个传说  谢谢
We all know the legend, thank you.
小时候就听说过了
We were told it as children.
现在不信  以前也没信过
I didn't believe it then, either.
它到底在那上面多久了
How long has it really been there?
没人知道到底多久了
Nobody knows exactly how long.
今天  你要把它拿回来
Today, you'll retrieve it.
祝你好运了  老弟
Good luck with that, Brother.
不可能
No way.
每一个尝试的人都死了
Anyone who's tried it has died.
传说说的很明白  能把剑从石头里
The legend's clear: whoever pulls the sword
拔出来的人  将统一不列颠  登基为王
from that rock shall be the King to unite all of Briton.
那剑插在上面几个世纪了
It's been there for centuries.
从未有人做到过
No one's ever done it before;
你为什么觉得我能做到呢
why you think I can do it?
因为没有人比你更迫切地
Because no one's ever needed to do it,
需要做到
as much as you do.
你的时机到了  相信你自己
This is your moment. Believe in yourself.
也许先训练训练...
Maybe with some training...
不行  必须是现在
No! It has to be now.
要是这么重要  你怎么不去做
If it's so important, why don't you do it?
别总依赖我  要学会靠自己的努力去争取
Stop pulling at me and start pushing yourself!
你有力量和智慧
You've strength and intelligence.
但如果不尽力  你就不会成为国王
But if you won't try, you're not my king.
那一切就都白费了
And everything will have been for nothing.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
你去哪了
Where were you?
我醒来的时候你不在我身边
I woke and you weren't beside me.
我早上喜欢出去散步
I like to walk in the mornings.
滚开吧  小淫妇
Move your arse, ya trout.
去哪散步了
Walk where?
林子里
The woods.
消息都传出去了
The word has spread.
我们已扬名在外  他们都开始送礼了
We've made our mark. They're sending gifts.
送回去
Send them back.
现在收礼有点早了  我们还没赢得地位
It's too early for gifts. Nothing's been won.
少来了  收礼哪有嫌早的
Ah come, come, it's never too early for gifts.
他们知道我们就要接手这片领土了
They understand who'll be in charge of the realm.
想表示对我们的敬意
They want to show respect.
等那男孩走了我们才配收这些礼
We'll deserve it when the boy is gone.
有人看见那男孩今早骑马离开卡米洛特
The boy was seen riding out of camelot this morning.
他们夹着尾巴跑呢
They're scurrying away.
你确定吗
And you know that for sure?
我知道恐惧能如何作用于人
I know what fear does to people.
我们将把卡米洛特废墟里剩下的人都赶走
We will drive all those that remain from the ruins of Camelot.
然后庆祝我们的新婚
Then we will celebrate our wedding
并为加冕礼做准备
and make preparations for our coronation.
拜托  承认吧  这多让人激动啊
Oh, come on, you've got to admit, it's exciting.
要是你在筹划打仗  而非庆祝
I'd be excited if you were planning battles,
我会更激动的  陛下
instead of ceremonies... My Lord.
我父亲能坐稳王位就是因为他从不自满
My father stayed King because he never became complacent.
希望我无需质疑我们结盟的决定
I hope I won't have cause to doubt our alliance.
准备好了吗
Ready?
兄弟连心  其力断金
Stronger together.
我在找我的儿子们  凯和亚瑟
I'm looking for my sons, Kay and Arthur.
你看到他们了吗
Have you seen them?
您是埃克特
You're Ector?
您是亚瑟的母亲
And you're his mother.
我是他的生母
I gave birth to him.
您妻子才是他母亲
But your wife was more his mother.
我为她的死感到非常遗憾
I'm so sorry for her death.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们总会想象您的容颜
We always wondered what you looked,
想象他会有多像您
how much of you was in him.
我们曾想过如果你来找他
We used to talk about what might happen
我们会怎么样
if you came to claim him.
但你却一直没来
But you never came.
我不能去  他们禁止我去找他
I couldn't. I was forbidden to search for him,
甚至不能说起他
or speak of him.
有人骑马来了
A rider approaches...
是啊
Of course.
打开大门
Open the gates!
出什么事了
What's going on?
有人想要拔出战神之剑
Someone's trying to pull the Sword of Mars.
亚瑟
Arthur.
管用啊  这办法管用
It's working! It's working!
加油  拉啊  凯
Come on, pull, Kay!
那是作弊
That's cheating.
这是创新
It's initiative.
很好  继续
Yes! Come on!
准备烽火
Prepare the beacon.
浪费木材  他得不到那把剑的
Waste of wood. He'll not get that Sword.
走开
Piss off.
用力
Come on!
我们成功了
We did it!
你说过我们的首要任务是保护国王
I thought you said our priority was to protect the King.
我站在这里
I've been on those rocks.
你却让他去冒险
You're sending him to his death.
即便他得到了石中剑  那不可能...
Even if he gets to the Sword, it's impossible...
不可能成功
can't be done.
他能成功
It can.
必须成功
It must.
我们已一无所有
We've nothing.
继续爬
Keep Going!
继续爬  亚瑟
Keep Going, Arthur!
你们在浪费时间  伙计们
You're wasting your time, lads.
他不会成功的
He'll never make it.
他会成功
He'll make it.
他们来观看传奇的诞生了
They've come to watch a legend born.
别停下  亚瑟  别停
Don't stop Arthur! Don't stop!
亚瑟  集中精力
Concentrate, Arthur.
用你的力量和智慧...
Strength and intelligence...
别再依赖于我
Now stop pulling at me
靠自己的努力去争取
and start pushing yourself!
好样的
Yes!
亚瑟
Arthur!
Arthur?
他还有呼吸吗
Is he breathing?
你成功了  我的孩子
You did it, my boy.
他成功了
He did it!
发信号  点亮烽火
Send the signal. Light the beacon.
告诉每一个子民
Tell everyone.
他们的新国王诞生了
The new king has come.
这不可能是真的
It can't be true.
如果他得到了众神之剑
If he has the Sword of the Gods,
人们将会为他而战
people will fight for him.
你以为我不知道吗
You think I don't know that?
那正是他今早出去的原因
That's why he rode out this morning.
你低估了他
You underestimated him,
你这懒鬼
you lazy cunt!
你竟敢那样说我
Don't you talk to me like that!
我们结盟了
We have an alliance
我的盟友不能那样说我
and my allies don't speak to me in that way.
如果你是个男人  我会杀了你
Now, if you were a man, I'd kill you.
现在我要换种方式教训你
I'm just going to teach you a lesson instead.
你是对的
You're right.
让他们看看你怎么掌控我
Show them how you control me.
来啊  你想怎样就怎样
Here, however you want. Do it.
行使你至高无上的权利
Assert your supremacy.
让他们看看你多强壮  干吧
They need to see you're strong. Do it!
来啊  我准备好了  干啊
Come on! I'm ready. Do it!
不  我有更好的主意
No. I've got a better idea.
你们需要休息
You all need to rest.
我们不会离开他
We're not leaving him.
如果你们累垮了对他无益
You're no good to him exhausted.
晚上我们轮流照顾他
We'll take turns to sit with him through the night.
如果他伤势恶化
If he worsens,
当值之人就叫醒其他人
whoever's on duty can wake the others.
做点什么吧
Do something!
你有魔法
You have powers!
治愈他
Fix this!
不行
No.
那你还有何用
Then what use are you?
你是个聪明的婊子
You're a clever bitch.
但你玩不过我  贱人
But you can't play me, woman.
放开我
Release me!
你将我引入你的城堡
You brought me into your castle.
你以为可以控制我
You thought you could control me,
达成你的目的
for your own ends,
但你错了
but you were wrong.
我们应该专注于尤瑟的杂种
We should be focusing on Uther's bastard!
你必须思考一下
You need to think
我们联盟的本质
about the nature of our alliance.
以及真正的力量之源
And where the true power lies.
别这样
Don't do this.
如果你没被狼吃掉的话
I'll talk to you in the morning.
我明早再来和你谈
Unless the wolves get you first.
你刚出生就离开了我
You've had a terrible loss
此事已无法...弥补
and nothing can... heal that.
但我可以帮你
And I could be useful.
虽然我们还不亲近
I know that we are strangers,
但我可以帮你
but I could help you.
我懂得运营城堡
I know how a castle is run,
我懂得帝王之道
and I know how a king should live.
我会辅佐你
I can do that for you.
求求你
Please,
求你让我赎罪
please let me atone for my mistakes.
我找过你
I searched for you.
你没来
You didn't come.
他错了
He is wrong.
谁错了
Who is?
他错了
He is wrong.
他没恶化  太好了
He's no worse. That's something.
你该去休息
You should rest.
我会看着他直到黎明
I'll watch till dawn.
我不想再有家人死亡  梅林
I won't have any more death in my family, Merlin.
他这样做了
He did this
你妻子的死才有价值
so your wife's death would serve the cause.
我才不在乎你的理想
I don't care about your cause!
我儿子的生命
My son's life
远比你的计划更重要
far outweighs any plan that you might have.
早啊
Hello.
你摔下了悬崖
You had a fall.
我做到了吗
Did I do it?
做到了什么
Do what?
你做到了
You did it!
你是无与伦比的
You were extraordinary!
我们达成共识了吗
Do we understand each other now?
是的
Yes.
好女孩
Good girl.
那男孩拥有了众神之剑
The boy has the Sword of the Gods
据说人们都归顺了他
and the word is that people rally to him.
我给了他五天时间
I've given him five dawns.
他以为可以智取我
He thought he could outwit me.
我的耐心到此为止
My patience is done.
我...不  是我们...
I... no, we...
我们今天就进攻
we attack today.
来吧
Come on.
运气好的话  我就让你骑我的马
If you're lucky, I'll let you ride on the back of my horse.
当心
Careful.
我知道
I know.
大家都没做到  我怎么就做到了
How did I do it, when so many others had failed?
你就是为此而生的
This is what you were born for.
尤瑟的高贵血统  埃克特的良好教育
Uther's bloodline, Ector's education.
你还能够学以致用
You used your knowledge.
这些都是你独有的
Only you have that.
你说得没错
You're right.
我做到了  是我
I did it. Me.
全靠自己
On my own.
也不全是
Nearly on my own.
你说过的一些话
Something you said.
要靠自己  不能依赖你
About pushing, not pulling.
可你怎么知道
But how could you know...
除非
unless...
剑是你插的
you put the Sword there.
那个传说是你编的  你知道
You created a legend knowing that, one day,
有一天会有人去征服圣剑
someone would conquer it.
向前看
Eyes round.
那把剑已经插在那里几百年了
That Sword's been there hundreds of years.
谁都不知道到底插了多久
Nobody knows exactly how long.
但你知道
Except you.
你头上有个包
You've had a bump on the head.
噢  感谢上苍
Oh, thank god.
不多说了
Oh, shut up.
要成为一国之王
If you want to be a king,
就得受一些磨难
you've gotta learn to take a few knocks.
虽然言不由衷  但总算有一次
Hate to say it, but you didn't need me.
你没需要我了
For once.
多谢
Thank you.
随时为您效劳  陛下
Your servant, My Lord.
好了  他们都在等你
Now. They're waiting.
谁
Who are?
他们都从远处看到你拔出了圣剑
They saw what you did, from afar.
刚开始只是有传言
In the beginning was the word.
后来一传十十传百  人们便都来了
And the word spread. And the people came.
现在我们要当着他们的面为你加冕
Now we'll crown you, in front of them.
现在加冕
You want to crown me now?
他们将成为你的军队
They'll be your forces.
把你奉为国王
Take your place as King.
她来干什么
What does she want?
我去对付她
I'll take care of her.
又来耍什么花招
What're you, the decoy?
我是来警告你们的
I came to warn you.
洛特知道了圣剑的事
Lot knows about the Sword.
你们活不到明天了
You don't have another dawn.
他就要进攻了
He's coming.
为什么要告诉我
Why tell me this?
摩根
Morgan!
好运
Good luck.
传下话去
Pass the word around.
洛特大军快来了  安排好一切备战事宜
King Lot is on his way. Everything must be prepared.
现在我们知道了时间  但不知他会怎么打
Now we know when; we just don't know how.
加冕礼绝不能有任何差池
Nothing must stop this coronation.
亚瑟  任命我为国王护卫
Arthur, make me your Champion.
命我为护卫  我会找到洛特
Make me your Champion, and I will find Lot
为你母亲报仇
and avenge the death of your mother.
国仇家恨一起报
For our family and country.
在下梅林  圣剑在此
It's Merlin! With the Sword!
今日  我等要向
Today, we pledge our allegiance
大不列颠之王宣誓效忠
to the King of all Britons;
正是他拔出了众神之剑
the one who removed the Sword of the Gods.
现在有请
I present to you,
你们当之无愧的国王
your undoubted King.
你是否愿意庄严起誓
Will you solemnly swear to rule the
将要秉承民众之
peoples of this realm according to their laws
律法  风俗 和正义
and customs and cause law and justice, in mercy,
慈悲地统治你的子民
to be executed in all your judgments?
我愿意
I will.
你是否愿意秉承天主教条
Will you maintain the laws of God
与马太福音
and the true profession of the Gospel?
我愿意
I will.
以此王冠为鉴  我宣布
With this crown, I anoint you
你为不列颠之王
King of the Britons.
请起  亚瑟王
Arise, King Arthur.
一提起列王  我总觉得他们是
When I hear of kings, I think of warriors,
为得到王位不惜大开杀戒的好战之人
coming to the throne through slaughter.
我亚瑟绝不是那种人
I am not that person.
但我深知那些人让人民损失惨重
But I have known loss at the hands of those men.
我不会重蹈覆辙
I'm something new.
今日站在诸位面前  我才明白
Standing here before you, I realize that.
我知道你们对我寄予厚望
I know I carry your hope in me.
而我  将在此地  卡米洛特
And I will establish, here at Camelot,
以一种新的方式统治你们  我的子民
a new way of ruling, for you, the people!
我今日之成就  都归功于我的家人
Everything I am, I owe to my family.
不仅是我的血亲
Not just my bloodline,
还有那些拥护我的人们
but those who raised me.
国不成家  则何以为国家
And a country is nothing if not a family.
因此  我召父亲与兄长前来
So, I call upon my father and my brother
共谋大业
to join me here!
没有兄长的督导
Without my brother's guidance,
我难以成器
I wouldn't be the man I am.
我请他督察整个王国
I demand he apply his stewardship to all the realm.
我任命我的兄长  凯  为英格兰元帅
My brother, Kay... Marshal of England!
每个国王都需要护卫
And every king needs his Champions.
在我的加冕礼上
And on my coronation,
我选择我的父亲埃克特
I choose my father, Ector.
他居功至伟
There is no greater man.
还有里昂提斯  他是我的救命恩人
And also Leontes, to whom I owe my life.
这不是我一个人的国家  是我们的国家
This is not my country. It is ours.
我是亚瑟·彭德拉根
I am Arthur Pendragon
能成为诸位的国王  我倍感骄傲
and I am proud to be your King.
你好
Hello.
敢问芳名
So, what is your name?
桂妮维尔
It's Guinevere.
我是亚瑟
Arthur.
我知道
Yes. I know.
咱们找个安静的地方说话吧
Let's find a quieter place to talk.
没想到还能再见到你
I didn't think I'd see you again.
据我所知  你能活下来实属运气
From what I hear, you're lucky to be alive.
那实在有点鲁莽
That was pretty reckless...
不过也很勇敢
and very brave.
谢谢
Thank you.
我喜欢你刚才说的那些话
I like what you said.
从没想过一位国王能说出那样的话
I never expected a King to say those things.
这算好事吗
Is that a good thing?
对我来说是的
To me it is.
高高在上的感觉如何
What was it like up there?
君临天下的感觉
All those people?
就像是我生命中第二次
Like, for only the second time in my life,
在正确的时间站在了正确的地点
I was standing in the right place at the right time.
那第一次在哪里
When was the first?
在海滩  遇到了初相识的某人
On a beach with someone I'd just met.
在这城墙里也能看到那片海滩
You can see the beach from the ramparts.
来  我带你去
Come on, I'll show you.
二十年前  你从我身边带走了他
You took him from me, 20 years ago.
可你看起来一点都没老
And yet you look no older.
是你的记忆捉弄了你
Your memory is playing tricks.
不  那晚对我来说记忆犹新
No. That night is branded on my soul.
你一点也没老  这怎么可能
You have not aged one day. How is that possible?
是不可能
It's not.
太美了
It is beautiful.
你在想什么
What are you thinking about?
未来
The future.
未来会怎样
What about it?
你就不担心这一切的重责
Don't you worry that all this
会改变你吗
responsibility will change you?
会把你压垮吗
Close you down?
你不说  我还真没担心过
I didn't until you just said it.
你说从这儿跳下去会死吗
Do you think you'd die if you jumped off here?
不会  我就是活生生的例子
No. I'm living proof.
这里可高多了  你确定吗
It's a lot higher. Are you sure?
只要避开岩石就行
As long as you avoid those rocks.
还有那些断树桩
And that stump.
当然  你绝不想撞到那些断桩
Of course you wouldn't want to hit that stump.
你觉得海有多深
How deep do you think that sea is down there?
想知道吗
Do you want to find out?
如果你跳  我也跳
If you do, I will.
准备好了吗
Ready?
一
One...
二  三
and Two, three.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
我就知道你不会跳
I knew you weren't going to do it.
如果你跳了  我肯定跳
I would if you had.
楼下玩得很疯狂
It is madness down there.
楼上也很疯狂
It is madness up here.
里昂提斯  认识桂妮维尔吗
Leontes, have you met Guinevere?
不认识
No.
桂妮维尔  这位是杰出的里昂提斯
Guinevere, this is the amazing Leontes.
其实  我们相识很久了
Actually, we've known each other a very long time.
孩提时  我们就是朋友
We've been friends since childhood.
她是我的未婚妻
This is my betrothed.
没错
I am.
太好了  恭喜
That's wonderful. Congratulations!
谢谢
Thank you.
她就是我找寻一生的唯一
I was just looking for her.
你们很幸运  幸运的一对
You're very lucky. A lucky couple.
这位勇士救了我的命
This man saved my life.
当然  他就是这种人
Yes, he does that.
那好吧  我该下去继续狂欢了
Well then. I should get back to the madness.
尽情享受吧
Enjoy.
敌军已经混进来了
They're already here!
凯  护驾
Kay! Protect the King!
快  这边走  快走
Leave! This way! Go, go, go!
站稳了  伙计
Stand strong men!
快把他带走
Get him out of here!
马上走
Out of here, now!
要想活命就给我让开
Out of my way and you live.
你不知道我是谁吧
You don't know who I am, do you?
我可不在乎你是谁
I don't care who you are.
你杀了我的妻子
I'm the man whose wife you killed.
那又怎样
And?
告诉我她的名字
Tell me her name.
什么
What?
那个被你杀害的女人的名字
The name of the woman you slaughtered.
最关键的是她已经死了
The only thing matters is she died.
她跪着过完了人生的最后时刻
She spent her last hours on her knees.
够了
Enough!
现在  去跟她作伴吧
And now you're going to join her.
父亲
Father!
不  不  不  不  父亲
Oh no, no, no no...no... Father...
把尸体拖到广场上去
Drag his body into the courtyard.
确保所有人都知道洛特王已经被打败了
Make sure everyone knows King Lot has been vanquished.
儿子们  我爱你们
My sons. I love you.
不  别死
No, please!
父亲
Father!
我试图与人结为联盟
I tried an alliance with a man.
但他失败了
But he was wrong.
人类不能助我夺得王位
Men are not my way to this.
我会另想办法的
I'll find another way to take it.
为什么你要夺走一切
Why do you need to take it at all?
从现在起  你的城堡将由我来保护
I'm placing your castle under my protection from now on.
以感谢你的警告
In gratitude for your warning.
我们不必反目成仇
We don't need to be opposed.
我们可以共谱大业
We can work together.
王位非你即我  不可能属于两人
It's either you or me. It can't be both.
为什么
Why not?
对你而言  这没什么
For you, this is nothing.
对我来说  这就是一切
For me, everything.
那晚  你看到了什么
What did you see in the night?
我知道那是什么  你呢
I know what it is. Do you?
别靠近它
Don't go near it.
千万别跟它有任何瓜葛
Don't have anything to do with it!
你在哪里
Where are you?
我所求更多
I need more.
告诉我  我该怎么做
Tell me what I have to do.